I'm nervous.
緊張してます
But it's cute.
でも可愛いっすね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's kind of like cleaning.
なんか、清掃な感じで
happy.
うれしい
I'm excited.
興奮しますね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
I heard that she's really slutty.
すごいスケベーって聞いたんですけど
picture?
え?
Have you heard of that?
そんなこと聞きました?
What do you think?
どうですかね?
Isn't that true?
そんなことないですか?
Maybe.
かもしれないし
I have a little surprise for you today.
今日はちょっとサプライズがあるんで
what?
何ですか?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
scared.
怖い
what?
何ですか?
That's scary.
怖いね
I see.
なるほど
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
nostalgic.
懐かしい
scared.
怖い
怖 い
It was a bit relaxing.
ちょっとまったりしてましたね
a little bit.
ちょっと
How was it?
どうでした?
I thought it was intense.
激しかったなって思って
Was it intense?
激しかった?
It was intense.
激しかった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's lewd.
スケベーですね
That's not true.
そんなことない
What is it?
なんですか?
Have you had sex in private recently?
最近プライベートでエッチしました?
Lately, yes.
最近は そうですね
There was a little.
ちょっとありました
Ah, there it was.
あ、あったんだ
I would like to hear more details.
詳しく聞きたいですね
good.
いい
What are you doing now?
今何してるんですか?
Usually.
普段は
I'm currently a student and have been going to pastry school for the rest of my life.
今は学生で、生涯で パティシエの学校に行ってます
To the pastry chef.
パティシエさんに
in the future?
将来は?
I want to be a pastry chef.
パティシエになりたい
It was Halloween recently, so I made a pumpkin cake.
最近はハロウィンだったので パンプキンケーキとか 作って
I did.
ました
The one you made is great.
作 ったやついいっすね
I want to eat it.
食べたいな
Do you want to eat?
食べます?
I just received chocolates from Godipo.
さっきゴディポの チョコもらいましたけど
You like it.
好きなんだね
I really like sweet.
甘いのめっちゃ好きです
I eat it all the time.
いつも食べます
Do you eat alone?
一人で食べますか?
They eat alone, and they want to eat together.
一人でも食べるし、 一緒に食べたいとか
Petruto?
ペトルト?
There's a kid I've been getting a little worried about lately.
最近ちょっと気になってる子がいて、
I thought I'd like to eat it with him, so I gave him something I made.
一緒に食べたいなと思って 作ったのをあげたりとか
Are you in love?
恋してるの?
I agree.
そうですね
I'm curious.
気になってます
There's someone I like.
好きな人がいるんだ
I have someone I like.
好きな人います
What kind of person are you?
どんな人ですか?
Well, it looks really scary,
え っと、 見た目めっちゃ怖いんですけど、
It seems like he's actually kind.
本当は優しいみたいな感じです
Are you from the same school?
同じ学校の人?
that's right.
そうです
A bit naughty.
ちょっとやんちゃ系な
But she's a mischievous type, but is she a sweets lover?
でもやんちゃ系だけど、 お菓子生か?
It's cute to throw away too.
捨てるのも可愛い
Making sweets reminds me of Gap,
お菓子作ってるのもギャップ思い出し、
He's a kind person.
優しい人です
That's right.
そうなんだ
Do you want to go out to eat together?
一緒にご飯行ったり?
I agree.
そうですね
I want to go home, Elro, etc.
帰りたいとか、 エルロとか
Isn't he also interested in me?
向こうも私のこと気になってるんじゃないの?
I agree.
そうですね
I don't lack confidence.
ちょっと自信がなくはない
Are you dating?
付き合うんですか?
付き合うの?
Will we date?
付き合うのかな?
Oh, did you have sex?
あ、エッチしたの?
Well, that's right.
えっと、そうですね
I did it properly.
ちゃんとしました
We're not dating though?
付き合ってはないけど?
We weren't dating, but we ended up doing it.
付き合ってはないけど、しちゃいました
Is that so?
そうなの?
A complicated relationship?
複雑な関係?
I agree.
そうですね
Maybe the order is a little reversed.
ちょっと順番が逆かな
It's an investment association.
投資協ですね
What is it?
なんですか?
Is that so?
そうですかね
It's nice to have someone you like, but is that really the case?
好きな人いいけど、 別 に、あれですか?
Is it okay to do it with someone you like?
好きな人とやるのは別に いいかな?
Like.
みたいな
You looked like you were feeling good just now.
さっき気持ちよそうな顔してたね
It felt good just now.
さっきは、 気持ちよかったですけど
Because I was happy.
喜んでたから
I didn't hate it.
嫌いじゃなかったです
It's true.
本当だよ
good.
よかった
satisfaction?
満足?
yes.
はい
Are you satisfied?
満足しました?
I feel quite satisfied.
結構満足した気がします
Well then, come back.
じゃあ、 帰ってきて
Go home.
ご帰宅
Were you satisfied?
満足したの?
Were you satisfied with just one?
1本で満足したんですか?
Are you only satisfied with one bottle?
1本満足ばかり?
What do you mean?
どういうことですか?
What did you say that for?
何のために言われたの?
satisfaction.
満足
I think I was satisfied.
満足したと思うんだけど
Were you satisfied with that level?
あの程度で満足したんですか?
That much?
あの程度?
That's about it.
あの程度です
I think it was quite intense.
結構激しかったと思うんですけど
There's more.
まだあるよ
Gear second, gear sambar for a bit.
ギアセカンド、ギアサンバーでもちょっと
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
What should I do?
どうしよう?
どう しよう?
What's up with this kid?
この子どうしてるんですか?
I'm worried about what to do.
どうしようって悩んでますもんね
What should I do?
どうしよう?
Is that so?
そうなの?
Are you with the person you are interested in?
気になってる人と 一緒なんですよね?
I agree.
そうですね
Which one was better with the person you were interested in?
気になってる人とどっちがよかったですか?
Which one?
どっちが?
Which one was better?
どっちがよかったですか?
Which one?
どっちが?
どっちかな?
It's a little scary, but you're satisfied, aren't you?
一応、 ちょっと怖い系だけど、 満足したじゃないですか?
Seems kind.
優しいみたいな
That was really good too.
そっちもめっちゃよかった
This one is also scary, but kind in a different way.
こっちも怖い系だけど、 違う意味で 優しい
kind?
優しい?
Have you become kinder?
優しくなった?
What do you think?
どうかな?
Really?
本当に?
Were you expecting a difference in what you could do again?
もう一回できるものの差が期待してたんですか?
One more time?
もう一回?
If one more time isn't enough, two more times will do.
もう一回じゃ足りなかったら、 もう二回でできるだけ
Was it pretty intense?
結構激しかったっけ?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
what up?
どうした?
What happened?
何があった?
what up?
どうした?
Why are you hanging out?
どうしてぶら出してるんですか?
Are you inviting me?
誘ってるんですか?
I haven't invited you.
誘ってないです
Haven't you invited me?
誘ってないの?
Won't you invite me?
誘ってくれないの?
Such beautiful breasts.
こんな綺麗なおっぱい
Didn't you get a good look at it just now?
さっきあんまりしっくり見れなかったんですか?
I've been busy.
忙しくてね
It was amazing just now.
さ っきすごかった
Was it amazing just now?
さっきすごかった?
Because I did something really terrible earlier.
さっきもひどくすごくするから
That's good.
いいもんね
Thank you very much.
どうもどうも
All at once.
一挙いられた
This is OK.
これOKですね
OK.
OKだ
embarrassed
恥ずか
Yes.
しい
It would be a waste to hide such nice breasts, so you should show them all.
こんな 良いおっぱい隠したら もったいないから 全面に出すべ
It's Ki.
き ですよ
I should go home like this.
このまま帰るべき
That's no good.
ダメそれ
It's so hard to walk that I shake.
歩くしんどくて揺れるじゃん
why?
なんで?
What's beautiful?
どこが綺麗なの?
Right away.
すぐすぐ
Aren't your pants wet?
パンツ濡れてない?
It's quite damp.
だいぶ湿ってるよ
No.
ダメだよ
It's quite damp.
結構湿ってますね
Were you excited?
興奮してたの?
My pants are wet and different.
パンツ濡れて変わってるもんだよ
Only here.
ここだけ
I'm also nervous.
俺もグリグリしてるから
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you really embarrassed?
本当に恥ずかしいの?
It's wet, isn't it?
濡れてるよね
It's not wet.
濡れてない
Really?
本当に?
This is glued on.
これ糊と引いてるよ
Look here.
こっち見て
It's being spread out.
広げられちゃってるよ
That's erotic.
エ ロいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
If you've come this far, even if you're embarrassed.
ここまで来たら恥ずかしがってもね
Aren't you better at having fun?
楽しんだほうが得意じゃない?
I missed you, but you didn't bring me sweets, so I was there.
すれちゃったけどさ、 お菓子持ってきてくれなかったから いた
I'll move it.
ず らするわ
nice.
いい ね
Cree is finished.
ク リー終わったね
Cree is really breathing.
クリーめっちゃ呼吸してるんだよ
It's wet, isn't it?
濡れてるよね
It moves easily.
簡単に動いちゃう
I just wore my Chin-chan.
さっき俺のチンちゃん履いたしね
Is that why?
だからか
Ah, like this.
あ、こんなね
I could have said it earlier.
さっき言えたんだもんな
It's wet.
濡れてるよ
It smells a bit.
ちょっと臭い
I'll scrape it out for a while.
ちょっとかき出しておくからさ
She has a really beautiful butt.
すっごい綺麗なお尻してる
I've got my hands on it.
ここ手ついて
I can see it being spread out.
広げられてるところ見られちゃってる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Really?
本当に?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
The important parts are cluttered though.
大事なところクパクパしてるけど
It's so embarrassing.
そんな恥ずかしいんだ
That's a really beautiful butt and legs.
めっちゃ綺麗なお尻と足だね
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Is it just embarrassing?
恥ずかしいだけ?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Okay.
いいよ
Only the top is cut off.
上だけ切れてる
Don't you see it?
見なくない?
You don't see it.
見ないじゃん
Don't look up.
上を見ないで
Where are the parts you are most proud of?
自慢のパーツはどこですか?
A proud part?
自慢のパーツ?
Where is it?
どこだろう?
Where are the proud parts?
自慢のパーツにどこ?
Where?
どこかな?
Absolutely.
絶対そう
What parts are you proud of?
自慢のパーツにどこかな?
I haven't seen such a beautiful butt in a long time.
こんな綺麗なお尻、久々に見た
Is it a good cup?
いいカップか
Good cup?
いいカップ?
Is it a nice cup?
いい カップか
It's a nice cup.
いい カ ップ だよ
Is that a good cup?
それがいいカップか
I see.
なるほど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?